Gallowwalkers is a action, horror, western film directed by Andrew Goth.
When a nun broke her covenant with God to save the life of
her unborn son, Aman, he was cursed for life.
As an adult, Aman has killed those who have crossed him.
But his curse brings his victims back to life and they pursue him for revenge, so Aman
enlists a young gunman to fight by his side against his undead victims.
Aman, played by Wesley Snipes.
Fabulos, played by Riley Smith.
Angel, played by Tanit Phoenix.
Apollo Jones, played by Steven Elder.
Mistress, played by Jenny Gago.
Kansa, played by Kevin Howarth.
Gallowwalkers is a 2012 American Western horror film written and directed by Andrew Goth, and starring Wesley
Snipes, Kevin Howarth, Riley Smith, Tanit Phoenix, Patrick Bergin, and Diamond Dallas Page.
Due to Wesley Snipes' tax problems, the film went through many
changes and delays and was completed in 2010.
It still had no official release until a 2012 screening at the
"Film4 FrightFest" festival in the United Kingdom.
It was released on DVD and Blu-ray in the United States in 2013, nearly
eight years after the film started production in 2006.
The film explores themes of nun, hair, zombie, skin, gunman.
The tone is dark.